{
  "name": "CoffeQuiz Part I",
  "quizItems": [
    {
      "quizItemId": 0,
      "question": "Which of these Statoil-countries exports the most coffee on a yearly basis? (i.e we can have a little Subsidiary in that country called Statcaff or CoffOil)",
      "alternative1": "Colombia",
      "alternative2": "Brazil",
      "alternative3": "Indonesia",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-11T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 1,
      "question": "What is the current best guess of the subduction rate in the area where Statoil holds acreage in New Zealand since start of Miocene, i.e last 20 million years?",
      "alternative1": "50 cm / 1 year",
      "alternative2": "5 cm / 1 year",
      "alternative3": "5 cm / 1000 year",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-12T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 2,
      "question": "Which is the most successful type of stratigraphical trap according to GCQ and the inhouse statistics over the last years?",
      "alternative1": "Distal front lap",
      "alternative2": "Side lap",
      "alternative3": "Proximal updip pinch-out",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-13T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 3,
      "question": "The Pre Salt play is hot in Basil these days, but what is the age of the salt?",
      "alternative1": "Selandian",
      "alternative2": "Albian",
      "alternative3": "Norian",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-14T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 4,
      "question": "How can you tell that this person is a geologist?",
      "alternative1": "He is licking a rock",
      "alternative2": "He has a rock proof glasses",
      "alternative3": "He finds the rock more interesting than the opposite sex",
      "answer": 1,
      "startTime": "2017-12-15T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 5,
      "question": "What is the name of the new amazing mega wow wow yeah yeah super duper collaboration software that we will have?",
      "alternative1": "Bluemoon",
      "alternative2": "Bluescape",
      "alternative3": "Blueoyster",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-18T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 6,
      "question": "What hydrocarbon type was expected to be found the AD-10  Block in Myanmar?",
      "alternative1": "Thermogenic gas",
      "alternative2": "Biogenic gas",
      "alternative3": "Oil",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-19T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 7,
      "question": "What was the outcome of the pre salt round in Brazil that was just finished?",
      "alternative1": "Statoil representative went to the wc and missed the 10 minute bidding",
      "alternative2": "Statoil emptied it’s pockets and made a successful bid",
      "alternative3": "Statoil tried it’s best but failed miserably",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-20T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 8,
      "question": "How many tcf’s of gas has been discovered in Area 1 & 4 held by Anadarco, Eni and others off shore Mozambique?",
      "alternative1": "18 Tcf",
      "alternative2": "108 Tcf",
      "alternative3": "1080 Tcf",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-21T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 9,
      "question": "What mineral are bananas generally thought to be a good source for? (although not necessarily true)",
      "alternative1": "Calcium",
      "alternative2": "Potassium",
      "alternative3": "Magnesium",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2017-12-22T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 10,
      "question": "What is the name of the Basin in India where Statoil was partner in a licence that made a big discovery, until about 2010-ish?",
      "alternative1": "Mannar Basin",
      "alternative2": "Konkan Kerala Basin",
      "alternative3": "Krishna Godavari Basin",
      "answer": 3,
      "startTime": "2018-01-03T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 11,
      "question": "Indonesia is a huge country comprising over 13 000 islands and many basins onshore and offshore. How many basins has a proven petroleum system in Indonesia?",
      "alternative1": "23",
      "alternative2": "33",
      "alternative3": "53",
      "answer": 1,
      "startTime": "2018-01-04T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 12,
      "question": "What peculiar geological feature can be seen in the shallower part on this 3D broadband seismic line?",
      "alternative1": "Hydrothermal Vents",
      "alternative2": "Basalt flow",
      "alternative3": "Remobilised Ooze",
      "answer": 3,
      "startTime": "2018-01-05T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 13,
      "question": "How many deep water (>500 m wd) exploration wells have been drilled in the Ceduna Basin?",
      "alternative1": "<5",
      "alternative2": "5-10",
      "alternative3": "10-20",
      "answer": 1,
      "startTime": "2018-01-08T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 14,
      "question": "Which famous geological site is this picture from?",
      "alternative1": "Dorset, England",
      "alternative2": "Kilkee, Ireland",
      "alternative3": "Avaldsnes, west coast Norway close to Utsira",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2018-01-09T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 15,
      "question": "How many kilometers is the strike slip offset along the Sea Gap fault in Block 2 Tanzania in Saffron time?",
      "alternative1": "7 km",
      "alternative2": "70 km",
      "alternative3": "700 km",
      "answer": 1,
      "startTime": "2018-01-10T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 16,
      "question": "What is the HC column height in the Pao discovery?",
      "alternative1": "200 m",
      "alternative2": "700 m",
      "alternative3": "1400 m",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2018-01-11T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 17,
      "question": "What is this very common diagram called that is used to differentiate between different source rock types?",
      "alternative1": "Van Koevarden diagram",
      "alternative2": "Van Halen diagram",
      "alternative3": "Van Krevelen diagram",
      "answer": 3,
      "startTime": "2018-01-12T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 18,
      "question": "Which one of these wells is not a discovery in Block 2 Tanzania?",
      "alternative1": "Well A",
      "alternative2": "Well B",
      "alternative3": "Well C",
      "answer": 2,
      "startTime": "2018-01-15T00:00:00+01:00"
    },
    {
      "quizItemId": 19,
      "question": "How many exploration wells have Statoil drilled this year until now and what is the success rate in %? Uncommercial discoveries not counted as success",
      "alternative1": "26 wells 46%",
      "alternative2": "30 wells 30%",
      "alternative3": "35 wells 20%",
      "answer": 1,
      "startTime": "2018-01-16T00:00:00+01:00"
    }
  ]
}